

Vũ Tiến Quý

.Net Developer

Date of birth: Jan 01, 1994

Gender: Male

Phone: 0868493546

Email: quy.vu.0101@gmail.com

Address: La Phu, Hoai Duc, Hanoi, Vietnam

Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vu-quy-181098177/

ABOUT

I'm a Back-End developer engineer with 3 years of experience. One year of Experience with Front-End. With my knowledge of Back-End, UI/UX. I enjoy solving Back-End, Front-End UX problems and creating the best user experience.

I also spend time learning new technologies and best practices to become a better developer.

I love reading books. My favorite books are C# in-depth, Concurrency in .NET Modern patterns of concurrent and parallel programming, and some others by Manning Publisher. There are some persons that I subscribe to on youtube like Nick Chapsas, or CodeOpinion...

EDUCATION

Sept 2012 - Sept 2018

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Major: Precision mechanics and optics

GPA: 2.52/4

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apr 2021 - Present

2NF

Developer: .Net

Finstro (Fintech, AU):

- **Description**: This is a B2B Finance System. The app provides lending services to other businesses and also helps users to keep tabs on how the debit funds are being used.
- **Responsibility**: Contributed to many important parts of the project. Example: optimizing the APIs(speed up to 3 times before), detecting vulnerabilities in BE code that lose user data due to processing multiple threading. Help our team members work better and improve the code quality.
- Technology:
- -- Front-End: Angular, Swift(iOS), Kotlin(Android)
- -- Back-End: .NET core, MySQL(RDS), DynamoDb.
- **-KeyPoints:** .NET core, AWS(S3, Code Pipeline, Cloudwatch, Cognito).

eShop_PhucVinh (Side Project):

- **Description**: This is an eCommerce system. The customer is PhucVinh Company. We make this application to manage the

product, staff, user, warehouse, before and after Sale...

- Technology:
- Front-End: VueJS.
- Back-End: .NET core, SQL Server, MongoDB, Redis, Redis Pub/Sub.
- *Responsibility*: Evaluating Back-End technology, designing the system architecture, database, infrastructure, and coding. Working directly with the end-user.
- Key Points: .Net Core, Microservice, CQRS, Redis Pub/Sub.

LaiChau E-Tolling (Side Project):

- **Description**: This is a toll collection project for the Border Gate of Lai Chau province. The Project's principal objective is to collect fees from vehicles transporting imported and exported commodities. The full System includes user administration, authentication, toll collection system, reporting ...The project is implemented under the microservice architecture.
- Technology:
- -- Front-End: Administrator website: Angular; Mobile App: Flutter.
- -- Back-End: .NET core, MySQL, MongoDb, EventStoreDb, RabbitMq.
- -- Desktop App: .Net Framework.
- *Responsibility*: Evaluating Back-End technology, designing the system architecture, database, infrastructure, and coding. Working directly with the end-user.
- *Key Points*: .Net Core, Microservice, DDD(Domain Driven Design), CQRS, Event Sourcing, Saga Orchestrator, CI/CD, Docker, Kubernetes

May 2020 - Apr 2021

HICAS

Developer: C#, Angular

Smart MTO(Material Take Offf):

- Description: This project is used for enterprise purposes. We take off the material using Yolo 4 and text using EmguCV (Tesseract).
- Technology: .NET Framework, Autocad .NET
- **Responsibility:** Using the .NET framework, take down the Symbol, and material on the drawing using an image processor(EmguCV, Tesseract). Find out the solution to recognizing the text, and reduce the time by up to 30%. Using multiple threading.
- **KeyPoints:** .NET Framework, EmguCV, Tesseract.

Synergis:

- **Description:** This is a system used for viewing the drawing on the browser, marking the markup and managing them.
- Technology: .Net core, Angular.
- Responsibility:
- --- Front-End: Integrate the Foxit Web SDK to view the drawing. Fix the Foxit library for customers' requirements.
- -- Back-End: Write the APIs, Improve the system with multiple threading management. Find out the solution for the issue: The

server is crashed if we have a lot of several file converting requests (out of memory).

- KeyPoints: Angular, .NET Core

Apr 2019 - May 2020

VietVuong Telecom

Developer: C#

- Electronic Toll Collection:
- **Description**: This is the ETC (Electric Tolling Collection) project. An autonomous road fee transaction system.
- Technology: .NET Framewok
- **Responsibility:** Find out the solution for measuring the vehicle length, Display VMS in the Vietnamese language. Code the Queue management, Multiple Threading.
- **Self-learning:** Spring Framework, Hibernate: Made the e-shop by using spring framework, hibernate, jQuery, and Java.
- **Self-learning:** ASP.NET Framework. Made the eShop using ASP.NET MVC. Using EntityFramework, razor. Database design

2018 - 2019

SODICK VietName

Electical Engineer

- Fix the electronic boards for the CNC machine. Create the program for machine running. I have been many times evaluated by direct superiors and foreign colleagues high in workability. During this time, I also opened classes to teach Arduino programming to students. And reach good results!

2012 - 2018

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Autobox Team leader

Student, team leader of auto box lab. Due to my passion for programming, II develop myself after learning to program. Arduino in the subject. I also studied myself and also help my classmates as well as the lower class in this subject and got good results

SKILLS

Language	English, Vietnamese
Developing Language	.NET, TypeScript
DevOps	CICD, Docker, Kubernetes

INTERESTS

I like reading books like C# in Depth, Concurrency in .NET Modern patterns of concurrent and parallel programming, and Microservices in .NET Core. You know, those books are made by Manning. I think you will like them like me.

Moreover, I like listening to music, some videos...

Also, I subscribed to some Developers on Youtube like Nick Chapass, CodeOpinion...